原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
改编自《冰与火之歌》
原著 乔治·R·R·马丁
第六季 第九集
权力的游戏
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：Silmar 草草 潇湘月影
■
翻译：盐湖凉开水 煮粥达人 泰斯
校对：泰斯·雪诺 Silmar   顾问：屈畅(ccxx)
时间轴：崽猪 加森 Avis
后期：吉吉·波顿  总监：泰斯·雪诺
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
尽管表象不佳  我想您会发现城市正在复兴
Despite appearances, I think you'll find the city's on the rise.
或许我们该去避一避
Perhaps we should take shelter.
弥林正在复兴
The city's on the rise?
弥林很强大
Meereen is strong.
市场已经恢复繁荣
Commerce has returned to the markets.
人民支持您
The people are behind you.
当然不是所有人民
Well, not all the people, of course.
世上没哪个统治者能赢得所有人支持
No ruler that ever lived had the support of all the people.
但弥林的重生也是这场战乱的根源
But the rebirth of Meereen is the cause of this violence.
奴隶主们不能坐观弥林成功转变
The Masters cannot let Meereen succeed.
如果弥林成功转变成没有奴隶制
Because if Meereen succeeds, a city without slavery,
没有奴隶主的城邦
a city without Masters...
就证明了没人需要奴隶主
it proves that no one needs a Master.
很好
Good.
可以开始了吗
Shall we begin?
我们有计划吗
Do we have a plan?
我要钉死奴隶主
I will crucify the Masters.
烧毁他们的舰队
I will set their fleets afire,
杀死他们的每一个士兵
kill every last one of their soldiers,
让他们的城市归于尘土
and return their cities to the dirt.
这就是我的计划
That is my plan.
你不赞成吗
You don't approve?
您曾对我说您知道您父亲是怎样的人
You once told me you knew what your father was.
您知道兰尼斯特大军兵临城下时
Did you know his plans for King's Landing
他打算怎样处置君临城吗
when the Lannister armies were at his gates?
大概并不知道
Probably not.
他告诉了我哥哥  詹姆又告诉了我
Well, he told my brother and Jaime told me.
他秘密储存了大量野火  在红堡的地下
He had caches of wildfire hidden under the Red Keep,
各大会所  贝勒大圣堂
the Guildhalls, the Sept of Baelor,
每一条主要通道的地下
all the major thoroughfares.
他要烧死城内所有人
He would have burned every one of his citizens.
忠诚的臣民和叛徒一道
The loyal ones and the traitors.
每一个男人  女人和孩子
Every man, woman, and child.
所以詹姆才杀了他
That's why Jaime killed him.
这完全不是一回事
This is entirely different.
您在谈论毁灭城市
You're talking about destroying cities.
这并非完全不同
It's not entirely different.
我提议一个变通的方案
I'd like to suggest an alternate approach.
我们曾提出与你和平相处
Once before, I offered you peace.
若你不是那么傲慢
If you had not been so arrogant,
本可以带一支船队回返故乡的
you could have returned to your homeland with a fleet of ships.
然而如今你只能徒步逃出奴隶湾
Instead, you will flee Slaver's Bay on foot
正符合你乞丐女王的身份
like the beggar queen you are.
我们是来谈投降条件的
We are here to discuss terms of surrender,
不是来当街对骂的
not to trade insults.
条件很简单
The terms are simple.
你和你的外邦朋友
You and your foreign friends will
退出大金字塔和弥林城
abandon the Great Pyramid and the city of Meereen.
你从克拉兹尼·莫·纳克罗兹那里偷来的无垢者
The Unsullied you stole from Kraznys mo Nakloz
将再次出售给出价最高的人
will remain to be sold again to the highest bidder.
你从克拉兹尼·莫·纳克罗兹那里偷来的翻译
The translator you stole from Kraznys mo Nakloz will remain
将再次出售给出价最高的人
to be sold again to the highest bidder.
大金字塔下的龙将被杀死
The dragons beneath the Great Pyramid will be slaughtered.
我们先前的沟通显然存在误会
We obviously didn't communicate clearly.
我们是来商讨你们的投降条件  不是我的
We're here to discuss your surrender, not mine.
我想这一定很困难
I imagine it's difficult
接受新的现实
adjusting to the new reality.
你的统治结束了
Your reign is over.
我的统治才刚刚开始
My reign has just begun.
龙焰
Dracarys.
你们可以选择
为这些从未为你们战斗和死去的奴隶主战死
或者回家去  跟亲人团聚
多谢你们的舰队
Thank you for the armada.
我们女王的确喜爱战船
Our queen does love ships.
上一次对话时  我们是达成过协议的
Now, last time we spoke, we made a pact.
你们违反了协议
You violated that pact.
向我们宣战
You declared war upon us.
尽管女王陛下天性宽厚
Though our queen does have a forgiving nature,
此事却不可原谅
this cannot be forgiven.
女王坚持你们中的一个必须死
Our queen insists that one of you must die
作为对你们罪行的惩罚
as punishment for your crimes.
感触总不那么真切  是不是
It always seems a bit abstract, doesn't it,
别人要死
other people dying?
他  应该他死
Him. He should die.
-对  他死  -他不是我们的人
- Yes, him. - He's not one of us.
他是个外人  出身低贱
He's an outsider, a lowborn.
他不能代表我们
He does not speak for us.
求你
Please.
开恩
告诉你的人这里都发生了什么
Tell your people what happened here.
告诉他们你还活着是因为陛下的恩典
Tell them you live by the grace of Her Majesty.
如果他们提出报复
When they come forward with notions of retribution
或是想恢复奴隶城邦从前的辉煌
or ideas about returning the slave cities to their former glory,
提醒他们
remind them what happened
风暴降生丹妮莉丝和她的龙在弥林做了什么
when Daenerys Stormborn and her dragons came to Meereen.
你不是非得在场
You don't have to be here.
我得在
Yes, I do.
我亲爱的妻子
My beloved wife.
我好想念你
I've missed you terribly.
谢谢你把波顿夫人安全送回来
Thank you for returning Lady Bolton safely.
下马  给我下跪
Now, dismount and kneel before me,
让你的军队缴械
surrender your army
并宣称我是真正的临冬城领主和北境守护
and proclaim me the true Lord of Winterfell and Warden of the North.
我就赦免你背弃守夜人的罪
I will pardon you for deserting the Night's Watch.
我也会赦免这些贵族背叛我家族的谋逆罪
I will pardon these treasonous lords for betraying my house.
得了  野种
Come, bastard,
你的人手  马匹都不够
you don't have the men, you don't have the horses,
你攻不下临冬城
and you don't have Winterfell.
何必带领这帮可怜人蒙受屠戮
Why lead those poor souls into slaughter?
没必要开战
There's no need for a battle.
下马  下跪吧
Get off your horse and kneel.
我是个仁慈的人
I'm a man of mercy.
你说得对
You're right.
是没必要开战
There's no need for a battle.
成千上万的人不用丧命
Thousands of men don't need to die.
你我死一个就行
Only one of us.
我们以传统的方式了结此事吧
Let's end this the old way.
决斗
You against me.
我听到过不少关于你的传闻  野种
I keep hearing stories about you, bastard.
北境人把你说得
The way people in the North talk about you,
好像史上最厉害的剑客
you're the greatest swordsman who ever walked.
或许你真那么厉害
Maybe you are that good.
或许不是
Maybe not.
我不知道我能不能打败你
I don't know if I'd beat you.
但我知道我的军队能击败你的军队
But I know that my army will beat yours.
我有六千人
I have 6,000 men.
你有多少  一半吗
You have, what, half that?
还不到吧
Not even?
是啊  你人数多
Aye, you have the numbers.
如果你的人知道你不肯为他们而战
Will your men want to fight for you
他们还会为你而战吗
when they hear you wouldn't fight for them?
不错啊  真不错
He's good. Very good.
告诉我  你会因为骄傲不肯投降
Tell me, will you let your little brother die
而让你弟弟枉死吗
because you're too proud to surrender?
我们怎么知道他真在你手里
How do we know you have him?
如果你想救...
Now, if you want to save...
你明天必死无疑  波顿大人
You're going to die tomorrow, Lord Bolton.
睡个好觉吧
Sleep well.
你妹妹她是个好女人
She's a fine woman, your sister.
我很期待她回到我床上来
I look forward to having her back in my bed.
你们都是相貌堂堂的汉子
And you're all fine-looking men.
我的狗都等不及见到你们了
My dogs are desperate to meet you.
我七天没喂它们了  它们都饿坏了
I haven't fed them for seven days. They're ravenous.
不知它们会先吃哪里
I wonder which parts they'll try first.
眼睛
Your eyes?
卵蛋
Your balls?
我们很快就会知道了
We'll find out soon enough.
那就早上再见了  野种
In the morning, then, bastard.
如果他聪明
If he was smart,
他就该守在临冬城里  耗死我们
he'd stay inside the walls of Winterfell and wait us out.
他不是那种人  他知道北境在看着他
That's not his way. He knows the North is watching.
如果其他家族觉得他软弱
If the other houses sense weakness on his part,
他们就不会再惧怕他了
they'll stop fearing him.
那他可不能接受  恐惧是他的力量
He can't have that. Fear is his power.
也是他的软肋  他的人并不想替他打仗
It's his weakness, too. His men don't want to fight for him.
只是被迫参战  如果他们觉得风向变了
They're forced to fight for him. If they feel the tide turning...
让我担心的不是他的人
It's not his men that worry me.
是他的马
It's his horses.
我知道骑兵能怎样摧残我们
I know what mounted knights can do to us.
你和史坦尼斯对付我们就像在雪地里撒尿
You and Stannis cut through us like piss through snow.
我们正在两翼挖战壕
We're digging trenches all along our flanks.
他们没法用史坦尼斯的战术对付我们
They won't be able to hit us the way that Stannis hit you,
也就是两翼合围
in a double envelopment.
钳形夹击
A pincer move.
他们没法从两边攻击我们
They won't be able to hit us from the sides.
很好
Good.
我们必须等他们先进攻
It's crucial that we let them charge at us.
他们人多势众  我们必须有耐心
They've got the numbers, we need the patience.
如果我们的中军佯装败走  他会乘胜追击
If we let him buckle our center, he'll pursue.
到时候我们就三面合围
Then we'll have him surrounded on three sides.
你真的认为那个混蛋会跟你单挑吗
Did you really think that cunt would fight you man-to-man?
不
No.
但我想激怒他
But I wanted to make him angry.
我要他全力进攻
I want him coming at us full tilt.
我们都应该去睡一会儿
We should all get some sleep.
去睡吧  琼恩·雪诺  明天要看你的表现
Rest, Jon Snow. We need you sharp tomorrow.
你见了敌人
So you've met the enemy,
拟定了战术
drawn up your battle plans.
是啊  尽力了
Aye, for what they're worth.
你对他的了解只是通过一次对话
You've known him for the space of a single conversation,
你和你的心腹顾问
you and your trusted advisors,
坐在一起制定计划
and you sit around making your plans
试图打败一个你不了解的人
on how to defeat a man you don't know.
我曾跟他一起生活
I lived with him.
我了解他的想法
I know the way his mind works.
我知道他有多喜欢伤害别人
I know how he likes to hurt people.
你就没有想过  我可能看得更透彻吗
Did it ever once occur to you that I might have some insight?
你说得对
You're right.
你认为他会掉进你的圈套
You think he's going to fall into your trap.
不会的  他才是设圈套的人
He won't. He's the one who lays traps.
-他太自负  -他最会耍人
- He's overconfident. - He plays with people.
这方面他比你厉害得多
He's far better at it than you.
因为他一辈子都在干这个
He's been doing it all his life.
是啊  那我这辈子干什么了
Aye, and what have I been doing all my life?
耍扫帚吗
Playing with broomsticks?
我在长城外对抗比拉姆斯·波顿更可怕的敌人
I fought beyond the Wall against worse than Ramsay Bolton.
我为长城抵挡比拉姆斯·波顿更可怕的敌人
I've defended the Wall from worse than Ramsay Bolton.
你不了解他
You don't know him.
那好  告诉我
All right, tell me.
我们该怎么办  怎么救回瑞肯
What should we do? How do we get Rickon back?
我们救不了他
We'll never get him back.
瑞肯是奈德·史塔克的嫡子
Rickon is Ned Stark's trueborn son,
他对拉姆斯的威胁比你这个私生子
which makes him a greater threat to Ramsay
和我这个女孩大得多
than you, a bastard, or me, a girl.
只要他还活着
As long as he lives,
拉姆斯统治临冬城的资格就会受到质疑
Ramsay's claim to Winterfell will be contested,
也就是说  他活不长
which means he won't live long.
我们不能抛弃我们的弟弟
We can't give up on our brother.
听我说  求你了  他想让你犯错
Listen to me, please. He wants you to make a mistake.
他当然想  可我还能怎么办
Of course he does. What should I do differently?
我不知道  我对战争一窍不通
I don't know! I don't know anything about battles.
只是请你不要正中他的下怀
Just don't do what he wants you to do.
真是个好建议
Aye, that's good advice.
你认为这是明摆着的事吗
You think that's obvious?
这当然是明摆着的
Well, it is a bit obvious.
如果你早点征求我的意见
If you had asked for my advice earlier,
我会建议你不要攻打临冬城
I would have told you not to attack Winterfell
先集结更多兵力  这也是明摆着的吗
until we had a larger force, or is that obvious, too?
我们何时才能有更多兵力
When will we have a larger force?!
能求援的家族我们都找过了
We've pleaded with every house that'll have us.
黑鱼帮不了我们
The Blackfish can't help us.
有现在这些人已经够幸运了
We're lucky to have this many men.
-这还不够  -当然不够  但我们只有这些
- It's not enough! - No, it's not enough. It's what we have!
兵力更悬殊的战争也有人打赢过
Battles have been won against greater odds.
如果拉姆斯赢了
If Ramsay wins,
我不会活着回去
I'm not going back there alive.
你明白我的意思吗
Do you understand me?
我不会让他再碰你
I won't let ever let him touch you again.
我会保护你  我保证
I'll protect you, I promise.
没人能保护我
No one can protect me.
谁也保护不了谁
No one can protect anyone.
你觉得有赢面吗
You think there's hope?
我从没见过波顿家的混蛋打仗
I've never seen these Bolton fuckers fight.
他们也从没见过自由民打仗
And they've never seen the free folk fight,
所以是的  我认为有
so, yes, there's hope.
你想为你的国王报仇  对吗
You want to avenge your king, don't you?
打败史坦尼斯的不是波顿家
It wasn't the Boltons defeated Stannis.
而是史坦尼斯自己
It was Stannis himself.
我敬爱那个人
I loved the man.
他提携了我  给了我用武之地
He lifted me up and made me something.
但有魔鬼在他脑袋里灌输邪门歪道
But he had demons in his skull whispering foul things.
-你见过那些魔鬼吗  -什么
- You saw these demons? - What?
不  那只是一种形容
No, it's a manner of speaking.
不是...真的魔鬼
Not... actual demons.
好吧  你敬爱史坦尼斯那个混账
Well, you loved that cunt Stannis
而我敬爱被他烧死的那个人
and I loved the man he burned.
曼斯脑袋里可没有魔鬼
Mance didn't have demons in his skull.
他没把人烧死  也没有听信什么红女巫
He didn't torch people or listen to some red witch.
我曾经相信他
I believed in him.
以为他就是那个带领我们度过长夜的人
I thought he was the man to lead us through the Long Night.
但我错了  跟你一样
But I was wrong just like you.
也许我们错在相信那些国王
Maybe that was our mistake, believing in kings.
琼恩·雪诺不是国王
Jon Snow's not a king.
对  他不是
No, he's not.
大战前夜我得好好喝一杯才能入睡
I need a good drink to help me sleep the night before a fight.
你想来点儿吗
You want some?
我有罐酸羊奶
I have a jug of sour goat's milk
比你们这些南方佬喜欢吮的
stronger than any of that grape water
任何一种葡萄水都有劲儿
you southern twats like sucking on.
谢谢  不用了  听起来不错
No, thanks. It does sound delicious,
但是我得保持清醒
but I better keep a clear head.
大战前夜我从来都睡不着
I can never sleep the night before a battle.
那你晚上做什么
So what do you do all night?
散步
I walk.
思考和散步
Think and walk.
一直走到离营地足够远的地方
Think and walk until I'm far enough away from camp
就没人听到我把肠子都拉出来的声音了
that no one can hear me shitting my guts out.
祝你拉得愉快
Happy shitting.
女士
My lady.
你没参加作战会议
You weren't at the war council.
我不是战士
I'm not a soldier.
你有什么建议吗
Any advice?
别打输了
Don't lose.
如果输了  如果我死了...
If I do, if I fall...
别把我复活
don't bring me back.
我得试试
I'll have to try.
我命令你不准复活我
I'm ordering you not to bring me back.
我不是你的仆人  琼恩·雪诺
I am not your servant, Jon Snow.
你在我的营地里  我是指挥官
You're in my camp. I'm the commander.
我侍奉光之王
I serve the Lord of Light.
我依从他的命令行事
I do what he commands.
你怎么得知他的命令
How do you know what he commands?
我尽可能地...
I interpret his signs...
解读他的示意
as well as I can.
如果光之王不想让我把你复活
If the Lord didn't want me to bring you back,
我怎么会成功呢
how did I bring you back?
我自身没有力量
I have no power.
只有他赐予我的  也就是你
Only what he gives me and he gave me you.
为什么
Why?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许你仅仅是
Maybe you're only needed for
他计划所需的一小部分
this small part of his plan and nothing else.
也许他是要你再死一次
Maybe he brought you here to die again.
什么样的神会做出这种事来
What kind of god would do something like that?
我们的神
The one we've got.
我们上次相见还是在临冬城  对吧
Last time we saw each other was at Winterfell, yes?
我好像记得你还嘲笑过我的身高
You were making jokes about my height, I seem to recall.
拿侏儒的身高开玩笑的人
Everyone who makes a joke about a dwarf's height
个个都以为
thinks he's the only person
只有自己想得到那些玩笑
ever to make a joke about a dwarf's height.
"贵族的高度"  "像你这么高的人"
"The height of nobility," "A man of your stature,"
"一个需要仰视的人"
"Someone to look up to."
开来开去都是那五六个玩笑
You're all making the same five or six jokes.
-那是很久以前的事情了  -没错
- It was a long time ago. - It was.
后来你过得怎么样
And how have things been going for you since then?
我猜不怎么样
Not so well, I gather.
很难想象如果一切顺利的话
Can't imagine you would have murdered the Stark boys
你会去杀史塔克家的两个男孩
if things had been going well.
我没杀那两个男孩
I didn't murder the Stark boys.
但是我作过的恶有过之而无不及
But I did things that were just as bad or worse.
而且已经付出了代价
And he paid for them.
看不出来
Doesn't seem like it.
他这不活得好好的
He's still alive.
我相信  在临冬城长大
It was complicated for you, I'm sure,
对你而言不容易
growing up at Winterfell.
不太确定自己的身份
Never quite knowing who you were.
但我们的人生都不太容易  不是吗
But then, we all live complicated lives, don't we?
你为我们带来铁舰队的一百艘船
You've brought us 100 ships from the Iron Fleet
还有水手
with men to sail them.
我想  你希望获得的回报是
In return, I expect you want me to support your claim
我支持你登上铁群岛的王座
to the throne of the Iron Islands?
不是我  是她
Not my claim. Hers.
为什么不是你
And what's wrong with you?
我不适合统治
I'm not fit to rule.
至少在这一点上我们能达成一致
We can agree upon that at least.
铁群岛以前有过女王吗
Has the Iron Islands ever had a queen before?
不比维斯特洛多
No more than Westeros.
我们的叔叔攸伦失踪很久后回来了
Our Uncle Euron returned home after a long absence.
他杀死了我们的父亲  夺走了雅拉的盐王座
He murdered our father and took the Salt Throne from Yara.
如果我们不走  他还会杀死我们
He would have murdered us if we'd stayed.
提利昂大人说你们的父亲是个很糟糕的国王
Lord Tyrion tells me your father was a terrible king.
在这件事上我们是一样的
You and I have that in common.
确实
We do.
并且他们都被篡夺者杀害
And both murdered by a usurper as well.
他们的船够吗
Will their ships be enough?
加上原来伟主们的船  也许够
With the former Masters' fleet, possibly.
勉强够
Barely.
铁舰队的船不止一百艘
There are more than 100 ships in the Iron Fleet.
确实  并且攸伦还在造更多的船
There are and Euron is building more.
他打算带给您
He's going to offer them to you.
那我为什么不等他呢
So why shouldn't I wait for him?
他想给您的不只是铁舰队
The Iron Fleet isn't all he's bringing.
他还想给您...
He also wants to give you...
他的大屌  我想这是他的原话
His big cock, I think he said.
攸伦的提议  同时也是婚约
Euron's offer is also an offer of marriage, you see.
两者不可只取其一
You won't get one without the other.
我想你的提议不包括婚约吧
And I imagine your offer is free of any marriage demands?
我没这个要求  但我怎样都行  真的
I never demand, but I'm up for anything, really.
他杀了我们的父亲  还打算杀我们
He murdered our father and would have murdered us.
一旦您有了他想要的  他也会杀了您
He'll murder you as soon as you have what he wants.
七大王国
The Seven Kingdoms.
全部
All of them.
你们不想要七国吗
And you don't want the Seven Kingdoms?
您的祖先打败了我们的祖先  夺走了铁群岛
Your ancestors defeated ours and took the Iron Islands.
我们请您还给我们
We ask you to give them back.
就这样
And that's all?
我们希望您帮忙杀死一两个
We'd like you to help us murder an uncle or two
认为女人不适合统治的叔叔
who don't think a woman's fit to rule.
合情合理
Reasonable.
要是所有人都开始要求独立呢
What if everyone starts demanding their independence?
她不是在要求  是请求
She's not demanding, she's asking.
别人也可以请求
The others are free to ask as well.
我们的父亲是邪恶之人  在座的概无例外
Our fathers were evil men, all of us here.
他们让这个世界变得越来越糟糕
They left the world worse than they found it.
我们不会这样
We're not going to do that.
我们会让这个世界变得越来越好
We're going to leave the world better than we found it.
你将支持我为七国的女王
You will support my claim as queen of the Seven Kingdoms
并遵守七国一体的原则
and respect the integrity of the Seven Kingdoms.
不许再行奸淫劫掠之事
No more reaving, roving, raiding, or raping.
那是我们的生活方式
That's our way of life.
不再是了
No more.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
手机APP搜索
人人影视字幕组
喜欢游戏吗  小家伙
Do you like games, little man?
我们玩个游戏
Let's play a game.
跑向你的哥哥
Run to your brother.
你越早跑过去
The sooner you make it to him,
就能越早跟他重逢
the sooner you get to see him again.
就这样
That's it.
游戏就这么玩
That's the game.
很简单
Easy.
准备好了吗
Ready?
去吧
Go.
不  你得跑  记得吗
No, you have to run, remember?
那是游戏规则
Those are the rules.
不要
Don't.
准备冲锋
Prepare to charge.
Prepare to charge!
-拉  -拉
- Draw! - Draw!
拉
Draw!
射
Loose!
冲
Go!
冲  跟上你们的指挥官
Go! Go! Follow your commander!
冲啊  杀啊
Run and fight!
搭弓
Nock!
-拉  -拉
- Draw! - Draw!
-射  -射
- Loose! - Loose!
上
Now.
骑兵  冲锋
Cavalry, charge!
-搭弓  -搭弓
- Nock! - Nock!
-拉  -拉
- Draw! - Draw!
我们会射中自己人  放下
We'll just kill our own men. Stand down.
-射  -射
- Loose! - Loose!
去传话...
Get word...
不要
No!
射
Loose!
-射  -射
- Loose! - Loose!
我们这么等着跟蹲坑拉屎有啥区别
We may as well be taking shits back here.
跟着我
Follow!
是时候了  上
It's time, go.
-谁拥有北境  -我们
- Who owns the North? - We do!
让我看看
Show me!
步兵  前进
Infantry, advance!
跟着我  小子们  冲破他们的阵线
With me, lads! Break their line!
救命
Help me!
-托蒙德  -把他弄回去
- Tormund! - Get him back!
步兵  前进
Infantry, advance.
两边
Both sides!
后退
Fall back!
去他的  来
Fuck this, come on!
我们回家
We're going home!
开门
Open the gate!
弓手上城墙
Archers to the wall.
-他们的军队没了  -我们的军队没了
- Their army's gone. - Our army's gone.
我们有临冬城
We have Winterfell.
他们没有人手攻城  我们只用等着就行
They don't have the men for a siege. All we have to do is wait.
弓手
Archers!
上城墙
To the wall!
你建议一对一决斗  是吗
You suggested one-on-one combat, didn't you?
我重新考虑过了
I've reconsidered.
我认为这是个很好的主意
I think that sounds like a wonderful idea.
我要把我弟弟安葬在墓窖里
We're going to bury my brother in the crypt
在父亲身边
next to my father.
琼恩
Jon.
他在哪里
Where is he?
珊莎
Sansa.
你好  珊莎
Hello, Sansa.
这就是我要待的地方吗
Is this where I'll be staying now?
不
No.
我们在一起的时光就要到头了
Our time together is about to come to an end.
没关系
That's all right.
你不能杀我
You can't kill me.
我现在是你的一部分
I'm part of you now.
你的话会烟消云散
Your words will disappear.
你的家族会湮没无名
Your house will disappear.
你的姓氏会消逝无踪
Your name will disappear.
所有关于你的记忆都将磨灭无痕
All memory of you will disappear.
我的猎犬绝不会伤害我
My hounds will never harm me.
你七天没喂过它们了
You haven't fed them in seven days.
你自己说的
You said it yourself.
它们很忠诚
They're loyal beasts.
的确
They were.
现在它们饿坏了
Now they're starving.
坐
Sit.
趴下
Down.
Down!
趴下  趴下
Down! Down!
趴下
Down!
■
人人影视字幕组
官方APP
更新下载手机搞定
讨论交流登陆升级
到各大市场搜索
"人人影视字幕组"
下载网址：app.zimuzu.tv
■